Hey, this is Houston.
Do you copy?
Copy Houston.
It's Christy. How's it going?
Hey, Christy,
it's great to hear your voice.
Sam's family wants
to connect with her immediately.
Is she nearby?
She's in the research facility.
- I'll just connect to her.
- Okay, copy!
Sam, you got a call from India.
Your call has been forwarded to a--
- Brother!
- Hello! Welcome, in-laws.
Son-in-law hasn't…
He's on the flight over here.
"Has Adhithi eaten?
Did Adhithi get some sleep?
Did Adhithi like the arrangements?
Did she like the handloom sari?"
In fact, he even inquired about you.
Oh, that's sweet of him.
You don't worry about anything.
I'll handle everything.
He will be here on time.
Why don't you have a drink with me?
It's okay, not now.
You carry on!
Let's go!
That was a close call!
- Come here, damn it!
- Come dance with me, Uncle.
You're dancing unaware of the situation.
And you're inviting me on top of it.
Uncle, he did call, right?
No one has been answering my calls.
How many times should I call them?
- When did you call them?
- Since this morning.
If it's morning here,
it's night out there.
It is only dawn for them now.
Uncle, call them now.
Hello?
Sachin, why aren't you answering my calls?
- Who are you?
- Huh? FBI!
- Haven't you left for the wedding yet?
- Who is getting married?
Bloody sinners! Are you guys drunk?
Uncle!
What are you guys doing?
The wedding is tomorrow. And I don't
see that you guys are serious about it.
Is this how you behave?
How could you guys be so irresponsible?
Everyone here is stressed out.
For God's sake, get here soon.
Please!
Uncle, it's my responsibility
to bring Idhaya to the wedding.
Please hang up.
- Hey, where's Idhaya?
- Idhaya?
Idhaya!
Where the hell is Idhaya?
- Hey, Idhaya?
- Let me check upstairs.
- Idhaya!
Hey!
O Heart of mine
Oh, my God! Look at him.
We're getting late for the flight.
Why aren't you guys ready yet?
Buddy, that's the spirit!
- My best friend is getting married.
- Yay!
What are you guys waiting for?
We only have
two hours for the flight. Scram!
Oh, damn, let's get ready soon.
I've found my way to you
Instead of packing,
why are you throwing it down?
Quickly pack up. We're getting late.
Hey, throw that away.
Here you go!
Your misguided thoughts
Left me drowning in sorrow
Like nectar in every flower,
My heart seeks you every day
Butterflies are fluttering
A game of hide-and-seek is on
Everything looks lush and green
Butterflies are fluttering
A game of hide-and-seek is on
Everything looks lush and green
Beautiful birds circle in our sight
O Heart of mine
You're one of a kind
My throbbing love
Hey, you work out, right?
- Hand it to me.
- Thanks!
- Where's the huge bag?
- Hey, I did not bring it.
- You never asked me to.
- Why do you do this, Priya?
I regret bringing you guys
on business class.
- Oh, God!
- Sir, please sit down.
- Aren't they supposed to serve us juice?
Ma'am, please!
- Hey, where are you going?
- I'm going to the loo.
- Do I need permission for it?
- Prabhu, go with him.
- He might jump off the plane.
- Two cannot fit in there.
Fine, I'll adjust
Hey, fool! Fool!
- Did you board the flight or not?
- What?
Bloody dirty pants.
Peg yourself to be a great actor?
- Hello?
- I'll rip you apart.
What's with the hello?
The wedding is tomorrow!
If you don't make it here,
you're as good as dead.
Send me a picture of you
sitting on the flight.
If the wedding gets called off…
Give me the phone.
Phone?
I can't give you my phone, sir.
It contains a lot of personal information.
I don't want your phone.
Give me back my phone.
I'm so sorry.
Same phone and same color.
Is your uncle very short-tempered?
Uncle?
Did my uncle call?
Did you answer the call?
He yelled at me in colorful words.
He said he'd kill you if you didn't
make it to the wedding tomorrow.
Sir, ask him why he's here
when his wedding is tomorrow.
I understand!
You're looking for a scapegoat
to narrate your flashback.
- Am I right?
- No, sir.
I'm not the man for it.
Please find someone else.
- Sir, the others here are foreigners.
- Yes, sir.
Our story is rooted in the native.
Only you'd be the right match.
I'm going to watch TV.
Sir, they offered an $800 coupon
because the TV is not working.
Didn't they offer you?
It's okay. I'll read a book.
Sir, that's a guide manual.
You have no choice
but to listen to our story.
- Yes, sir.
- Sir,
you're tailored to listen
to a flashback.
Wearing shades, a suit,
and sitting next to us.
Sir, it's a love story.
And it's very interesting.
It'll be a time-pass for you.
And a venting session for us.
Sir, even the supporting
actor has two love stories.
- Hear us out, sir.
- Yes, sir.
What's the run-time?
Sir, the first half runs
for 1 hour and 23 minutes.
But the second half is trimmed
to 1 hour and 20 minutes.
Sir, we can complete the movie
within 2 hours and 43 minutes.
Start the film, guys!
We're a mix of 80s and 90s kids.
We're the last chapter
of a slower, gentler world.
Before the world began to race,
even doing nothing felt like happiness.
Back then, happiness was simple.
Lying on the rooftop, gazing at the sky.
Even though it's not much,
our hearts were lighter.
Friends were not profile pictures
or status updates.
But the one who knocks on the door
to call out to play.
No cafe latte or filter coffees.
Five bucks Popsicle,
and two bags of Lays.
That was our world.
Even cycling felt like
we were the King and Queen.
When the street lights come on,
it's time to get back home.
The lights coming on were our deadline.
But the same lights
were our childhood guardian.
When technology advanced,
we embraced and adjusted to it.
Right from the ringing of landlines
to this generation's seen status.
But our world wasn't a virtual one.
The scent of rain and sand,
open playgrounds,
our mother's voice calling out to us…
Those were our ring-tones.
Back then, life wasn't loud but light.
We're bearing both versions of the world.
From the time when VHS tapes
gave us irreplaceable memories.
We'll never get those days back.
However, it hasn't left us.
They're still alive in us.
It's alive in our smile, memories…
That indescribable feeling
when an old song slows your heartbeat.
We're the last simple generation.
But we're the first magic generation.
Hey, Idhaya, hot water is ready.
Quickly take a shower.
Uncle, let me watch some more TV
and then take a shower.
How long will you wear these dirty pants
without taking a shower?
- Uncle, let me watch TV for some time.
- Stop watching TV up close.
I don't have parents.
But I have my uncle.
He's everything for me.
Why are you guys late?
- I woke up late, dude.
- Run! Run!
- Me too.
- Once again, they're late to school.
- Come.
- Sir!
The last bell has rung,
and everyone is rushing in.
But you guys are happily taking your time.
In our school lives,
we all have one favorite teacher.
Affectionate, caring, and close to us.
Yes, beautiful, too.
And that's what
Geetha teacher meant to me.
My English teacher.
Prabhu, my tooth came off.
Then rush and bury it
without anyone knowing.
Why?
Only then will a new tooth grow.
Are you guys telling the truth?
Why? Aren't you aware of it?
I don't know.
Hey, don't eat the seeds.
A tree will grow inside your stomach.
Are you guys telling the truth?
- Hey, he's got twin swirls on his head.
- Yes!
That means he'll marry two wives.
Are you guys telling the truth?
Good morning, students!
Good morning, teacher!
In this year's annual day event,
who is willing to participate?
Hey, don't raise your hands.
It'll be humiliating on the stage.
Idhaya!
- Aren't you interested?
- I'm interested, Teacher.
Good!
Even Prabhu and Dravid are interested.
Very good!
- Check if it's clear now.
- Hey, is the transmission clear?
No!
It's not clear yet, Uncle!
Wait a minute!
It must be clear now.
Now?
What are they doing, guys?
They're planning to have a baby.
How do you know about this?
Didn't you see them kiss?
Hey, Idhaya!
So what if they kissed?
Don't you know
that kissing can lead to pregnancy?
Are you guys telling the truth?
Aren't you aware of it?
No, I know about it.
Still, let's clarify with brother Sachin.
You're right.
Brother will give us clarity.
That's right, guys!
Kissing will lead to pregnancy.
Don't you guys know?
I'm ashamed to call you guys my juniors.
Damn!
How would we know, brother?
That's why we came to you.
I have to teach you guys everything.
Fine, there's nothing I can do about it.
Because you're like
younger brothers to me.
Now we're going to witness
the fancy dress competition
of our 1998 Annual Day celebration.
First of all,
we're welcoming The Hanuman.
Good evening, I'm Abraham Lincoln.
I'm the 16th President
of the United States of America.
Thank you.
Hello, everyone!
I'm Netaji Subash Chandra Bose.
A freedom fighter of India.
Jai Hind!
I am… Neil Armstrong…
I am…
Neil…
Armstrong…
Idhaya!
What happened?
I'm right here beside you.
Speak confidently.
That's a small step for a man.
One giant leap for mankind.
You spoke brilliantly, Idhaya.
It was amazing.
Thank you, Teacher.
Don't you know
that kissing can lead to pregnancy?
Uncle!
How are babies born?
Hey, dirty pants!
Holy shit! What are you saying?
Idhaya, it's a very big mistake.
Shall we start from one?
- So, I was scared since then…
- One.
…thinking if Geetha teacher's stomach
will start growing.
Nothing, Teacher.
You're behind three months.
- Hey, hold the baby for me.
- I won't!
Hey, hold the baby!
Hey, Idhaya!
Why is he running scared?
Hey, it's raining!
Good morning! Good morning!
Good morning, Teacher!
How were your summer holidays?
You guys are no longer in your 4th grade
but you have graduated to the 5th grade.
I was scared after looking
at Geetha teacher's stomach.
This year we have a new student
in our class.
In that moment, I decided that
Geetha teacher's child is my child.
It's our child.
I decided to take care
of her and the child.
May I help you?
- Oh, do you want to help me?
- Yes!
Okay.
Hey, let's go inside.
Teacher, what happened to you?
- What happened?
- Please call for an auto.
Idhaya, hurry up!
Auto! Auto!
Please help me.
What happened, son?
She's in labor.
We have to go to the hospital.
Is it your mother?
- No!
- Then who?
- Idhaya!
- Teacher!
I'm coming, ma'am.
You'll be fine, Teacher!
Be careful…
Nurse!
Bring a gurney, it's an emergency.
- Teacher, please don't fear.
- Hold the umbrella.
Come on, hurry up!
Brother, where can I find a phone?
Go straight and take the last right.
Kids, I've informed your teacher's family.
They'll be here soon.
Your folks must be looking for you guys.
Let's go.
I appreciate it.
You guys did so much for your teacher.
It's not for our teacher.
But for his wife.
Almost everyone in this world
has had a crush on a teacher.
That's the inception of unrequited love.
Fine, let's go home.
Hey, why is he getting emotional
like 'Idhayam' Murali?
Hey!
Let's go. There'll be more things
in life to get emotional about.
Get in!
After that,
I never saw Geetha teacher.
I was told that she quit her job
and moved to another city.
That was the last day
I saw Geetha teacher.
Where was her husband
while you were signing the form?
Sir, he was a sincere shepherd.
He was abroad herding white sheep.
He left a pregnant woman alone
on the verge of delivery.
He must be a classic jerk.
Indeed, he's a jerk.
Sir, after that breakup, his tender
heart was torn into many pieces.
I understood!
Leave out love stories
that didn't work out.
Just narrate the ones that worked out.
Today, we'll be discussing corrosion.
You must be familiar
with the rusting of iron.
Green patches on a copper vessel.
And brass vessels.
Hey!
- The bell will ring, right?
- Yes, it will ring.
What if it's broken?
I will ring it myself.
…most commonly with oxygen.
Sit down, please.
Let me finish my explanation.
Then I can allow you to go.
Corrosion is a natural process.
Hey, will he let us go or not?
Hey, he'll let us go.
Be patient for five minutes.
…stable chemical state.
Please stand for the prayer.
- Our Father…
- …who art in heaven…
- …lead us not into temptation…
- …but deliver us from evil.
- Amen!
Okay, boys! See you all tomorrow.
Where is he rushing off to?
Who is he?
Where does he go with him every evening?
He comes to pick him up daily.
Dude, he's having something.
- Let's inquire what's happening.
- Hey, don't go.
He looks dangerous.
Don't be scared!
Hey, I'm running away.
Hey, he's looking at us.
Let's go away.
Hey, turn around casually.
Let's go.
Why are you scared of him?
- We're getting late.
- Hey, I was praying for us.
Ride faster.
- Idhaya!
- Coming!
Bye, Uncle.
Don't go on an empty stomach.
At least have some tea.
Oh, no!
- I'm getting late, Uncle.
- Stop acting. Come here.
Two things I love the most in this world.
- One is your tea.
- What's the second one?
- Dude, come on!
- Oh, no!
I won't reveal it.
- Love you. Bye, Uncle.
- Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey, reveal it.
In the evening, we have practice.
Don't forget.
We have a match coming up.
- Hey, I have to go.
- Bye!
Dravid, bye! Prabhu, bye!
Bye, guys! Bye, bye, bye!
Idhaya.
- Hi, guys! When did you come?
- Just now.
Meet my friend, Juju.
Hi.
Hey, Idhaya.
Let's go. Boys are waiting
at the pitch to practice cricket.
Hey, Juju has come here to meet me.
He'll feel bad.
Yes, bro! Don't take him away.
I'll be bored.
- Hey, Smack--
- Hey, let's go. Let's go.
Switched off or not, I won.
Why did you switch it off?
You are always hanging out with him.
You go away with him in the evening.
Lately, you've been avoiding us.
Why are you friends with a rowdy?
Juju is my friend.
Where do you both go every evening?
Go, Juju, ride faster!
Hey, we're late. Hurry up!
Dude, why are you always late?
That guy is grumpy. He'll yell at us.
Live it up! We're the boys!
Here, hold this! Let's go!
- I'll go first!
- No, I'll go first!
That's my shot!
Yes!
Why is your girl standing idle?
- Hey, Coach!
- Hey, why are you guys late?
Sir, tire puncture.
- Tire puncture, you say.
- Yes, sir.
- Sir, were you plucking grass?
- No, sir.
- That shot was really nice.
- Really?
Son, eyes over here.
I was observing the balls, sir.
Wow! Observing balls?
- Why not bat?
- Bat…
- Bat, sir.
- Oh, you have it already.
- No more coming late. Okay?
- Okay, sir.
- Today's game went well.
- Yes!
Thank you, Coach.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye, Coach.
Damn!
The court is this way.
Everyone is holding a book,
but you don't have one.
We're not here to study.
I'll take one from him.
Oh, no, my book!
I'm happy I got to see my girl.
I'm going to talk to her today.
Thirty one.
What is 31?
You have told me 31 times
that you will speak to her.
But you haven't till now.
I feel confident today
that I'll speak to her.
At least I will borrow
the focus guide from her.
Hey, come on, come here…
Juju!
Are you the gift fate gave me?
- It's over!
- 32.
Come on! We'll do it tomorrow.
Shut up! You're doing it on purpose.
Hey, come on, come here
Are you the gift fate gave me?
Does anyone have a doubt about
Newton's Law, which we learned yesterday?
Sir!
Would you please also teach us
Newton's second law of motion?
Good, this is what a good student is.
No one else is asking a question.
Imagine when we're cycling…
I have an idea
to make our girls turn around.
- What idea?
- Watch me.
- Sir!
- Look, everyone is turning around.
- I don't know anything.
- I don't know, either!
- What is it?
- Sir, I have a doubt.
What is your doubt?
- Gautham asked you a doubt.
- Yes.
If you explain it again,
it'll be helpful.
If you could repeat Gautham's question…
I will give you the answer.
My doubt is cleared, sir.
It's cleared, sir.
- It's clear. Absolutely cleared.
- Oh, clear?
He was asking for the sake of it.
- So, you understood?
- Yes, sir.
Fine, now share with us.
I understood, sir. I understood!
- Okay.
- "Okay" is his answer.
- Okay, sir.
- Sit down.
Everyone turned around.
Juju, you're amazing.
It's a fantastic idea.
Wondering why the coach is drinking cola?
How many of you like to drink cola?
Sir, me! Me!
So, all of you!
Good! Good! Good! Good!
So, this can is your target.
Now, you should serve to hit the target.
Whoever fails to serve properly
will be served by me.
Okay?
Sir, how's that possible? The target
is quite far! Shall I bring it closer?
What were you doing
all these days at practice?
Now, serve!
Aim at the bloody can.
Why are you meddling with the balls?
Come here!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Go to the women's court
and pick up balls.
Okay, sir. Thank you.
Why is he so happy about it?
Next, you!
Juju!
Now, you serve!
If I miss,
will I be given the same punishment?
You? Missing the target?
- I have confidence in you, kid.
- Okay.
Hail, Sania Mirza!
Wow! Very good, my boy.
- Thank you, sir.
- Tennis is in your blood.
Sir, I'd rather pick up the balls.
I appreciate that you're willing
to climb the ladder ritually.
- Go ahead.
- Sir, I'll pick up the balls.
- I said go.
- I want to pick up the balls.
- Go, damn it!
- Sir, I want to pick up the balls.
If you'd like to know
how important this formula is…
Using this--
Is he sleeping?
Hey, wake up!
Are you coming here to sleep?
- No, sir.
- This is an important problem.
Do you know about this problem?
Go! Go and derive the problem.
This question appeared 13 times
in the Public Exam.
Are you guys aware of it?
That fellow is sleeping in class.
Why didn't any of you wake him up?
- Hey, he's solving the problem.
- Yeah!
Fantastic, Juju.
- Hey! Hey!
- When did you learn it?
Damn it! You wrote
the question again on the board.
- Hey! Hey, buffalo!
- He found out!
What have you done?
Why did you rewrite the question?
- Sir…
- Hey, move aside.
Sir, what are you doing?
Sir, he solved the problem.
So I'm taking notes.
Damn you, he has written everything wrong.
He solved it, it seems!
Why are you guys torturing me?
- Which school do you go to?
- I don't go to school, but to college.
- College?
- Polytechnic College.
Polytechnic.
Why were you scared of me?
Whenever you came to pick up Idhaya,
you used to have something.
It's nothing but candy.
- Candy?
- Haven't you tried this candy?
It looks like mummy this way
and daddy upside-down.
How can you not know about this candy?
But you always rev your bike aggressively.
If I don't rev, it'll switch off.
That's why I kept revving.
But you turned around and glared at us.
- I saw you doing it.
- I don't have a rear-view mirror.
I turned around to see
if any vehicles are incoming.
- Do you want me to die?
- So, you're not a rowdy?
- I'm a rowdy, it seems.
- He may look rugged.
- But Juju is like a baby.
- Super!
Buy him diapers on discount.
Dude, we're getting late for the match.
Let's go.
Let's go!
Hi!
- Do you follow me everywhere I go?
- Do you leave us everywhere you go?
It's an unlucky bench.
No point in sitting here.
Fine, we'll manage.
- Why would he say that?
- He's trying to irritate us.
Only from this bench is the view amazing.
Students who are willing to volunteer
for Tsunami Relief Funds
are asked to register their names.
- What are you doing with the physics book?
- Everything is science, dude.
- …as visitors are…
- Look, he's got social science.
Chellammal Higher Secondary School.
St. John's Anglo Indian School.
St. Joseph Girls Higher Secondary School.
- Volunteering students…
- Hey, it's your girl's school!
Please meet the PT Master,
Mr. Valluvan.
- Wow!
- First time in a girls' school.
- Boys, fall in line.
- It's a first time for me as well.
Hey, there are only girls
in the girls' school.
Hey, were you expecting boys?
Hey, we're here to see Sam.
- Somehow, I should meet her.
- Sure, dude.
- Boys!
- Sir.
Why are we here?
We're here to pick up.
He meant we're here to pick up
the money for the relief funds.
Yes, sir, Tsunami relief fund.
- You see, this is a girls' school.
- Yes, sir.
So, make sure your
emotions are in control.
- Yes, sir.
- I'll control.
- Understand?
- Yes, sir.
- Come on, boys. Let's go.
- Come on, boys.
Mummy! Daddy!
- Silence!
- Sorry, sir.
These are all the important questions.
Please note it down.
Ionizable ions are molecules that exist
outside the coordination sphere.
Hey, dude, I saw Sam over there.
What are you doing over here?
Are you sure?
- Then who is she?
- I actually saw her over there.
Perhaps they are conducting
combined classes.
- Excuse me, ma'am.
- Yes!
- For Tsunami Relief Fund.
- Go ahead!
Students who wish to donate can go ahead.
- I don't have money.
- You don't?
Not an issue.
It's all our money.
Here you go. Drop it.
Oh, baby, you be taking my breath away
Pushing me far away
Making me drift away
Teasing me every day
I'll keep knockin your door
Until I really feel
The thrill of first love
Oh, baby, you be taking my breath away
Pushing me far away
Making me drift away
Teasing me every day
I'll keep knockin' your door
An unspoken love, raging within
An endless quest,
A heart filled with unrest
Will this wound ever heal
If we stay silent?
Will I overcome my shyness?
Will love prevail?
Time came to a standstill
We've been stealing glances every day
My steps always find their way to you
Sleep has deserted me
My yearning keeps growing
My body trembles because of you,
My love
Hey, come on, come here
Are you the gift fate gave me?
Just your thoughts
Lift me off the ground
Just you… only you…
I'll stay by your side forever
You smile every day
Till your lips hurt
Oh, baby, you be taking my breath away
Pushing me far away
Making me drift away
Teasing me every day
I'll keep knockin' your door
Until I really feel
The thrill of first love
Oh, baby, you be taking my breath away
Pushing me far away
Making me drift away
Teasing me every day
I'll keep knockin' your door
Until I really feel
The thrill of first love
Oh, baby girl
When moonlight fills the sky,
I want you with me
Shall we soar through the blue skies,
Close together?
All through the night,
Our dreams become one
I've completely lost myself
In this bliss
Time came to a standstill
We've been stealing glances every day
My steps always find their way to you
Sleep has deserted me
My yearning keeps growing
My body trembles because of you,
My love
Hey, come on, come here
Are you the gift fate gave me?
Just your thoughts
Lift me off the ground
Just you… only you…
I'll stay by your side forever
You smile every day
Till your lips hurt
Oh, baby, you be taking my breath away
Pushing me far away
Making me drift away
Teasing me every day
I'll keep knockin' your door
Until I really feel
The thrill of first love
Oh, baby,
You be taking my breath away…
I'm thinking of inviting him.
What do you think?
Shall I invite him?
Invite him. It'll be fun.
Idhaya!
Tomorrow is my birthday.
I've invited my close friends home
for a party.
If you could come, it'll be great.
Isn't your name Juju?
- You often bring comedy to class.
- Yeah.
He always does this with his hands.
Oh, she has noticed me.
- You, too, are invited.
- May I join too?
I'm good at comedy.
- Please come.
- Okay.
- Okay, bye.
- Bye.
Dude, this is super!
Super, it is!
You see, come again.
Come again.
Dude, I'm really excited.
- Hey, shush!
- Okay.
Hey, you guys are going overboard.
Hey, come on, come here
Are you the gift fate gave me?
IDHAYAM MIX
It doesn't look like a birthday party
but a wedding.
She mentioned a special invite,
but there are so many people out here.
Yet she invited you.
So, it's definitely special.
It is special!
Hey, Sam is here.
Hi! Hi!
Why is she ignoring me?
She is busy tending to the guests.
Listen, is the cake ready?
It's getting late.
Hi! Juju, my boy!
Okay, are you guys
on a special invite, too?
Dude, manage the situation.
Yes, sir.
- Everyone has been invited?
- Yes, sir.
Group invitation?
What did you tell him?
Why did she invite him?
Sit down!
- Hey, move a bit.
- Stop squeezing in.
Hello! Welcome!
Please sit down. Please!
Fine, tell me, who are you guys?
Why did you stand up?
Please sit down.
Dad, they're my friends
from the coaching class.
Oh, is it?
- Dad, Mom was looking for you.
- Please have a drink.
Please have some juice.
Please have.
You were upset
that she didn't talk to you.
Now, see, she brought you juice.
Hey, how come you are here?
Hey, dude, I got a special invite.
Special?
So, she's bringing juice for everyone.
Oh, no!
- Juice?
- I was thirsty, so I gulped it down.
- Sorry.
- Please take one more.
Thanks!
- Please have a drink.
- Okay.
Hey, drink slowly.
She brought you juice twice.
- Hello, sir.
- Ignore him, guys.
- You guys arrive at the party spot on.
- Ignore him!
He's torturing us.
Hey, forget about him.
She brought us juice twice.
It is special.
You give her the gift and propose to her.
It'll be a success.
Juju! You propose without
a gift and make it a success. Okay?
Okay.
- Hey, Juju.
- What is it?
Please come and help me.
I don't want to.
- Someone will see us.
- Come on, Juju!
I was trying to pick her up.
But she's picking me up, dude.
Wait here. I'll be back soon.
She's making the first move.
Don't mess it up.
Go! Go!
Guys, he's so slick.
I was about to come and speak to you.
But you beat me to it.
Juju, please wrap this gift.
- Gift wrap?
- Yeah.
- Is this why you called me?
- Yes.
- Here I come.
- Wrap these separately.
Why are you separating the love pigeons?
She's smiling.
Okay, I'll wrap them.
Can I get sellotape?
- Sellotape?
- Wait, let me check.
I'll check.
Check over there.
Come on!
Over there.
I found it.
Hey, what are you looking at?
Are they twins?
Yeah, they're twins!
- Who was at the coaching class?
- Samantha.
- Who was at the tennis class?
- Samyuktha.
- Twins?
- Yeah!
You didn't know?
You're kidding, right?
Hey, please shut up.
- Juju?
- Idhaya, don't give her the gift.
Give the CD to the girl
who came to the coaching class.
How was the class today?
Because of you,
I had to attend the coaching class.
I did not study for the test.
Hey, Dad is here.
Shall we leave?
Happy birthday to you…
Hey, I told you many times
not to use my clothes.
Likewise, don't touch my makeup.
Get lost!
This is the problem Juju hid behind
a rewritten question.
Is it?
Dude, you fell in love with the girl
who attended the coaching class.
Moreover, it was she who noticed you.
The girl who came to tennis class
ignored you.
You propose to the girl
who came to the coaching class.
That's the right thing to do.
- He's right.
- Yes, dude, that'll be right to do.
As you're twins
you guys must be having fun.
We used to switch places
and attend coaching and tennis classes.
How is it possible?
They could recognize you easily.
You guys don't believe me, right?
Wait!
Juju, Idhaya, please come over here.
Why is she calling me?
What's with her?
Who's the coaching class Sam?
Identify who.
Only today did we know they're twins.
How do we identify her?
Go ahead, give it a shot.
Hey, Idhaya, I was the one who invited you
at the coaching class.
See, I told you.
He won't be able to recognize.
You girls are repeatedly hurting him.
Are you single? Or twins?
I'm not a twin.
- But I'm committed.
- Hi, baby.
Brother!
- You were saying something.
- It's okay.
Brother, I heard it.
- Single and all…
- Let it go.
Bro, it's okay to say it.
Aren't you guys in a relationship?
Why are you nagging me?
Annoying people
hurting us again and again.
Idhaya! Idhaya!
Hey, Idhaya, what happened?
Open the door.
Hey, Idhaya, say something.
Hey, what happened?
What happened to the guys
from those two benches?
They are absent, sir.
I don't know what to do after 5 p.m.
After that, I stopped going
to coaching and tennis to see her.
Because I thought it was one,
but I fell for two girls.
I'm clueless with whom I fell in love.
I fell in love with only one girl.
But I lost…
That's an interesting plot twist.
Even Korean dramas couldn't compete.
It's a new concept.
Now, I'm laughing about it.
Back then, it hurt me a lot.
How did you manage
to fall in love again?
Sir, do you know what the medicine
for love failure is?
Is there a medicine for it?
It's falling in love again.
We moved to Chennai for our college.
My uncle moved with us.
The days when we graduated
from college and had no jobs.
We're coming for a live telecast
on Thanga Uncle's terrace
to watch the Cricket World Cup final.
Dearest Sachin Tendulkar.
Sweetheart Sehwag.
They're entering the pitch.
Hey, I'm going to whack you.
Priest, wait and watch, in the future,
Tamil commentary is going to be worse.
And you'll be laughing at it.
Hey, if they had employed our people,
they would've rocked it.
Isn't cricket already
under your people's control?
Please calm down.
Uncle, you're something else, I say.
You're telecasting the match on the
terrace and making tea in the kitchen.
I wanted to watch the
match at the stadium.
I couldn't get tickets.
Also, I had saved some money
to watch the match.
Since I couldn't make it to the stadium,
I wanted to bring
the stadium atmosphere right here.
So, I installed a screen upstairs.
Venu, sentiment, is it?
What sentiment?
During the 1983 World Cup,
Nallapadiandavar
stood with one leg just like this.
He's following the same sentiment.
Mr. Venu, don't put your leg down.
If India wins the World Cup today…
I'm going to order three big pots
of briyani from Charminar Briyani
and give it as food donation.
You'll be the first one to give
briyani as donation.
- Are you serious?
- Yes!
What's happening upstairs?
You have installed a screen and
are telecasting the match like a movie.
Don't you know you must inform
the Ward Councilor about it?
After the 83's, only now
we're getting to see the World Cup.
Even the Prime Minister is waiting
at the stadium to see them win.
And you're here whining about the
clerk and the counselor. Oh, God!
Even now, you won't invite me
to the match, right?
Please come and watch.
Who's stopping you?
The match is for everyone.
Please come and watch.
Serve it to everyone.
Hey, Uncle is here with the tea.
We can expect a sixer.
Hey, move aside.
Here comes Ghambir,
bowlers are going to tremble now.
That's a fantastic straight drive.
- Go and serve tea to everyone.
- First, you take a cup.
Dear, are you seriously in love with him?
Uncle, she might say no.
Please go and serve tea.
A lot!
Now this is what you call a match!
- Here, have it.
- You must not have beer on the roof top.
The boss can't digest milk.
Do you have a pickle?
Pickle?
Uncle, those goons are having booze.
And they're asking for a pickle
to have with beer.
It's wrong to have liquor
when women and children are around.
And on top of it, you've asked
for pickles. Leave from here.
How dare you remove us from here?
- I ought to!
- How dare you lay your hands on us?
Hey! Uncle! Uncle!
Brother, why are you getting angry?
Watch the match!
Hand me the bottle,
I'll put it in the fridge.
Once India wins,
we'll have drinks together.
You think India is going to win?
My foot!
Hey, Sachin is out!
Gone! And they're expecting a win!
As long as Dhoni is there,
the match won't end. Wait and watch.
Dhoni…
Brother, you can talk about us
all you want.
But don't speak ill of Dhoni.
Why? Is Dhoni a great player?
There go 4 runs!
And that's a fantastic shot.
Left-hand batsmen hit
is flying towards the trophy.
The fans are stunned by this shot.
Is it going to Sri Lanka or India?
Bring it on!
Come on, come on!
Once again, Gautham Ghambir
delivered a fantastic shot.
That was a fantastic shot.
The ball hit the boundary,
and auntie here is yelling.
Hey, don't block the projector.
That's great, guys!
Is this okay?
He got a gap
and has been scoring 4s continuously.
Amazing game, I say.
Virat Kohli is proving he's also in
this game by scoring boundaries.
Kohli's wicket was caught
like a goalie by Wilson.
The champion batsman Yuvaraj Singh, of
this World Cup series, is coming to bat.
That's a plot twist!
Idhaya, what happened?
First, remove his shirt.
- My eyes are burning.
- What happened?
Bring out the vehicle.
We must take him to the hospital.
- Hey, open your eyes.
- Idhaya! Idhaya!
Buddy, watch out!
Please have him sit carefully.
Fire struck his eye, Doctor.
Please check.
He's not able to open his eyes.
Sir, please open your eyes slowly.
I'm putting some drops.
- He should be fine.
- Dude, is it burning?
Of course!
- Hey, check what the score is?
- Yeah, score!
Look at him, Doctor.
He's more concerned
about the match than his eyes.
Hey, please calm down, dude.
Hey, it's 224/4.
- Where is Uncle?
- I don't know.
Uncle!
And the score is 277/4!
Everyone witnessed
Dhoni's winning shot on TV.
But I witnessed it in her eyes.
Please follow these drops for two days.
Don't make a wrong prescription
while celebrating India's victory.
Hey, Ammu, India won!
Dhoni scored a fantastic sixer
in the last ball.
Why haven't you left yet?
Sachin Bro!
I am ashamed
to call you guys my juniors.
Damn!
- You became a doctor?
- What are you guys doing out here?
This is what happened.
When will you guys change?
Still starting fights everywhere.
Brother, forget about it.
Why are you wearing a coat?
- I'm a doctor.
- Doctor?
Didn't you say kissing leads to pregnancy?
How did you become a doctor?
It's not believable.
Believe me. I'm a Doctor.
Are you serious?
A doctor in our family.
- I feel proud.
- Hey, take your hands off me.
In fact, doctors are truly great.
They make a lot of sacrifices.
- Yes, we work around the clock.
- Wow!
- But as a doctor, everything--
- Hold it right there.
You aren't so nice.
- Why are you praising doctors now?
- Brother, you don't get me.
- Sachin!
- It's a great profession--
What are you doing?
It's getting late. Let's go.
- Who is that, bro?
- My girlfriend.
- Your girlfriend?
- Yeah!
Stop lying to us.
Hey, guys,
these people are my school juniors.
- Hi!
- This is Lado, and this is Ammu.
- Hi.
- And they're my college juniors.
Hi!
They don't believe me
that you're my girlfriend.
- Is it?
- Yes!
When you say a beautiful girl like me
is dating a guy like him,
- people may find it hard to believe.
- Hey, that's enough!
I was just kidding. Relax!
Is your eye okay now?
Much better!
If the pain persists,
please come back tomorrow.
Okay.
I'm here to meet the girl I like.
- My eyes are cured now.
- Yes!
It won't be nice
if I don't bring her anything.
Why don't you buy a rose
and a greeting card for her?
- He's right!
- Hey! Get out of here!
He's giving lame old ideas.
- We'll do something new.
- Hey, the rose might--
Rose, greeting card,
and gifting a pair of pigeons…
It's all an old concept and is outdated.
You must think fresh and trendy.
I doubt following the trend…
Brother, please help me out.
She's in labor.
Please help me with her.
- Don't think. It's an emergency.
- Why us?
- Hey, let's check it out.
- Madam, bear a little, we're almost there.
- Ma'am, watch your step.
- Someone, please help!
Brother, bring out the gurney.
Instead of waiting, you could carry her.
- Please carry her.
- Hey, carry her!
Don't be scared.
- Watch out.
- Carry her.
- Come on, carry her.
- This way.
- Watch your step.
- Please be careful.
Brother, come along.
Brother, it's not always necessary
for an auto driver to help during labor.
- You too can help her.
- Get lost!
Dude, you thought
you didn't get her anything.
But God has graced you with a huge gift.
Hey, ask which way the labor ward is.
- Doctor! Over here.
- Careful.
- She's in labor pain. Check on her.
- It's an emergency.
Her pulse is high.
- Where's the gurney?
- No need for that.
Bring her over to that room.
Careful! Careful! Slowly.
- Nurse, quickly check her blood pressure.
- Yes, Doctor.
Don't worry. You'll be fine.
- Nurse, prep for the procedure.
- You're okay. Doing great!
- Let's go.
- Check if we have all the medicines.
- Why are you still standing over there?
- Sir?
How long are men going to keep avoiding
being by their wives' side during labor?
Go and witness the struggle
she's going through.
- Oh, no, you have got it wrong.
- It's wrong. Come with me.
- Nurse, I'm not her husband--
- Come on!
- Please hear me out.
- Go inside!
Turn around. Wear this.
Is this your first pregnancy?
Previous pregnancy, C-section,
or any complications?
What's her blood group? A, B, O?
- Any allergies?
- Yeah, she sneezed on her way here.
- When did she go into labor?
- The vehicle just arrived.
- I'm asking about labor pains.
- Don't worry. You'll be fine.
Bend down.
He does not know anything!
- Hurry up! I can't bear the pain.
- It's okay.
- Nurse, quickly prep the delivery tray.
- It's ready.
Bloody man,
how could you not know anything?
This pregnant lady's
curse won't spare you.
Go and give her some courage.
Go ahead, man!
Hello! Please be brave.
- Please be brave.
- Hold his hand.
Hold it tight!
- Please be brave.
- I'm on my way, Doctor.
- Be brave.
- Push, push. You can do it.
Take a deep breath.
- Doctor, she's fully dilated.
- Okay.
- Push! Push!
- You can do it!
Come on. Come on.
One more push.
Why do you have your back
turned to your wife?
- Something is not right.
- You're right!
A woman comes in an auto in labor.
And he'll carry her to the ward.
And he stays back during the labor.
I can't believe it.
- Very wrong!
- He's always been this person.
Right! When he was 10,
he signed for his teacher.
Hey, why didn't you tell them
you're not her husband?
They never let me speak.
Moreover, her husband wasn't with her.
I felt very bad for her.
Mom would've struggled
the same way, right?
Hey, it's a comedy scene.
Don't turn it into
a mother-sentiment scene.
Do you think
Amudha would've misunderstood me?
Sounds like Idhaya likes her a lot.
Nothing like that.
I couldn't get you married
to the girl you like.
But do you think
I wouldn't know who you like?
Why is she calling me now?
Hello?
Oh, no!
What are you saying? Where?
I'll be right there!
What happened?
- What happened?
- Lado and Amudha have no other business.
They got caught by the traffic police.
Ignore it!
What are you saying?
Let's help them.
Basically, when girls get caught and cry,
they let them go.
But our women are arrogant to the max.
They would've run their mouth.
And got caught.
Bro, Amudha is out there.
Uncle, make him understand.
Yes, you guys carry on.
I'll take care of the booze.
- I'll take care of Uncle.
- Didn't you say we must help others?
Now what? Only if you
come along will others follow.
Please, come with me.
- He's a nuisance.
- Sachin, even the police would spare them.
But he won't spare us.
Let's get them.
- Hey, Idhaya, let's go after this drink.
- Let's go!
Lately, women get drunk
and cause a ruckus.
- Yes, sir.
- Hey, Policeman!
Do you think drinking alcohol
is only men's right?
- Stop talking nonsense!
- Please shut up.
- No one gets out of the car.
- Okay, dude.
Everyone, wait here.
Please stop talking.
How could he speak so disrespectfully?
How dare he say whatever he wants?
Hello, how dare you call me a dog!
I won't insult the dogs
by comparing them to you.
- Lado, please--
- What happened?
Look, he's going overboard.
- Please calm down for a minute.
- Where's Sachin? Call him.
Lado, please calm down for a moment.
What happened?
I was driving the car.
They checked and asked me to go.
But she spoke out of turn.
This police officer
looks like trouble to me.
- Yes!
- Oh, she's a doctor, is she?
That doesn't give her the right
to speak down to the police.
How could she call me a dog?
- Sir, please forgive them.
- Why should I listen to you?
- Get to the side.
- Sir, I know my rules.
Only the co-passenger was drunk.
The driver wasn't drunk.
Why are you holding them?
Talking rules, is it? Super!
- Sir, please understand…
- Sir! Sir!
- Sir!
- What's the issue?
Sir, it's a DD case.
I'm investigating, sir.
Sir, only the co-passenger was drunk.
The driver wasn't drunk.
They're causing unnecessary problems.
Sir, he's distracting you.
Don't believe him.
Hey, stay normal.
Sir.
You've become a nuisance lately.
- Send them away.
- Thank you, sir.
Get in, let's go.
Lado, get inside the car.
Super! Idhaya solved the issue.
Hey, did you see my nephew?
He smartly handled the situation.
Smart, my foot!
Who's going to drive us home?
- Yes! Who's going to drive us?
- Is my mouth stinking?
- It's not stinking.
- Not at all, Uncle.
Now we've become friends of the police.
I'll drive.
Come on, drive, Uncle.
Uncle, we should arrive home
before they do.
Watch me drive now!
- Hey, ask them to leave.
- Leave!
- Drive, Uncle.
- Don't you know who we are?
- Uncle, why are you bringing it up?
- The gang that went before us…
- Yes!
…we're part of the same gang.
- He's a doctor.
- His tattoo says it too.
There's a sticker that says so, too.
Sir, there's a sticker.
A sticker doesn't prove
that you're a doctor.
Why is everyone
announcing themselves as doctors?
How dare you
sit inside the car disrespectfully?
Step out of the car.
Why would you get us into trouble, uncle?
Step out!
Step out of the car.
- Is he a doctor?
- Exactly, sir.
I think he doesn't believe you.
Say a few medicine names aloud.
Anacin, Crocin, Dolo
650, and Azithromycin.
See, he's a doctor.
Vicks Action 500, Paracetamol,
Vicks, Halls, Strepsils.
- Are you a doctor too?
- Halls?
Then how did you end up
in the police department?
Hey! Even a grocery store owner
can list these medicines.
Naming these medicines won't prove
you're a doctor. Get inside the car.
- Come on, let's go!
- Hey, where are you going?
Get inside this car.
- This one?
- Get inside this vehicle.
- Come on, get inside.
- Oh, no…
Come in!
Welcome home!
- Would you like to have something?
- What's this mess?
We got caught by the police
but you guys here were
chilling and boozing.
- Hey, calm down.
- Dude.
- Dude, we got caught by the police.
- Hey, Lado!
- Can you hear me?
- Hello! Hello!
- Yes, I can. Tell me.
Who's it? Is it Sachin?
Give it to me.
Hello! What happened?
We trusted Uncle to drive
and got caught by the police.
- Who's speaking?
- Aww, so sad!
- So sad!
- Yes, baby!
You'd better rot out there.
What did you tell me
when I called you for help?
- Hey, hey, babe!
- Don't say anything.
- Don't you call yourself a boyfriend.
- Dad's calling.
Your dad?
- Go to the roof top and talk.
- I noticed empty bottles here.
- Baby, please send someone to help.
- Who are you talking to?
Give me the phone.
- Be careful, dear.
- Okay, Dad.
Please eat on time and sleep.
Please go to sleep.
Sure, dear!
I'm going to sleep now.
- Lado?
- She slept.
- Take care.
- I'll call you in the morning.
- Okay, dear.
- Okay, bye, Dad.
It was Dad.
Asking about my
whereabouts and activities.
He takes care of me like I'm a child.
How about your family?
No issues in my family.
It's always fun for sons.
That's not the case.
I don't have parents.
I'm sorry, Idhaya.
It's okay. I have my Uncle.
He's equal to a hundred parents.
He's great at it!
What's this DTV?
Oh, this?
It's our local cable TV channel.
My Uncle and I dream of
making that into a satellite channel.
- Super!
- Thanks!
Would you like to have something?
No!
Can I get a simple cup of tea?
Not sure about a simple cup of tea, but
I can get you the best tea in the world.
Would you adjust?
- Okay.
- I'll bring it.
How's it?
What's the special ingredient
of the world's best tea?
Add tea powder to boiling water.
Then add a piece of ginger
and sprinkle Tulasi over it.
Finally, add lots of love…
If you have this tea, you won't forget
its taste for the rest of your life.
You added a lot of ingredients,
but did you add sugar?
Sugar?
Shall I add sugar and bring it back?
It's okay.
I'm liking this taste.
Sorry.
From now on, every cup of tea
will remind me of this one.
- You mean this sugarless tea?
- Yes!
With dreams in tow,
I came to tell a story
With memories lingering,
I stood in a different hue
Through you,
I saw miracles beyond reality
You made me feel happiness
Unknown to me
The heavens, vast and infinite…
Won't a tender drizzle grace me?
And in it…
My soul yearns to be drenched too
Where friendship thrives, sorrow fades
The heart carries no weight
The path unfolds in bloom
When you're by my side
No path is found unfelt
No love exists unbroken
No scar is too deep
When it belongs to the tale
With dreams in tow,
I came to tell a story
With memories lingering,
I stood in a different hue
Through you,
I saw miracles beyond reality
Without friendship, where is peace?
What moonlight can life offer?
Hand in hand, we drift like fireflies
My heart is veiled in the morning mist
Where the heart dwells,
Time stands still
Time flutters by on delicate wings
Some journeys turn beautiful
When hearts unite…
Lara Dominic,
do you take Sachin as your husband?
- Hey, say no.
- Lado, no!
- Say no!
- He brought a Father!
- Yes, Father!
- No…
- Sachin, do you take Lara--
- Yes, Father!
- Can I kiss the bride?
- Wait, wait, wait!
Looking for this?
Where friendship thrives, sorrow fades
The heart carries no weight
The path unfolds in bloom
When you're by my side
No path is found unfelt
No love exists unbroken
No scar is too deep
When it belongs to the tale
With dreams in tow,
I came to tell a story
With memories lingering,
I stood in a different hue
I request Doctor Noran
to distribute the convocation certificates
to the Department of Gynecologists.
Dr. Lara Dominic.
- Brother, you look happy!
- Congrats, Sachin, bro.
Dr. Priyanka.
- Wow! Wow! Wow!
- I am a doctor now.
From now on,
you'll handle the pregnancies.
And I'll handle the infants.
Bro, what do you mean?
She's a Gynecologist,
and I'm a Pediatrician.
- Oh, right!
- Ah, I get it.
So, this was your plan all along.
Well planned.
- Not bad!
- Dr. Amudha.
Hey!
How long will you keep romancing
through just your eyes?
Open your mouth
and profess your love for her.
I will!
When are you going to tell her?
She's more scared than you.
You must initiate.
I, too, wish to propose to her.
I will propose when the time is right.
This is your last chance.
She is going back to her hometown.
For God's sake, propose to her now.
If you miss now, she won't return.
I will propose to her
before she leaves town.
Enough?
He will never say it. I'll tell her.
- Hey!
- Stop being stupid.
I'm not the old Idhaya anymore.
Wait and watch,
this time I'll tell her.
All the best!
- What time is your train?
- At night, 8 pm.
So, Uncle, what's next?
It's her life.
She must make the decision.
What are you thinking about?
Didn't you say you're moving
to the UK and settling down there?
No, Prabhu,
I'm thinking of settling down in India.
I can't miss being in Chennai.
Moreover,
I can't leave Dad alone and go far…
So, is it marriage next?
She has to take a call about it.
Dear, do you like any doctor on campus?
Let's get you married to him.
No, I may marry anyone except a doctor.
Okay, right!
You marry as per your choice.
My only wish is for him
to look after you well.
- Yes, yes.
- Sir, as per your expectations,
to find a groom
who'd take good care of your daughter,
we at Wedding Art wish you the best.
This is Wedding Art…
- You guys keep talking. I'll bring my bag.
- Okay, Dad.
- Why, guys?
- Just for fun!
Hey, go and speak to him.
Try impressing your future father-in-law.
- Go, dude.
- Oh, really?
What are you looking at, sir?
It'll be beautiful
if you all stay together like this.
Ten years down the line,
we'd be the same.
If it happens, it'll be wonderful.
But it's not practical.
In the future, everything will change.
Each of you will pursue
different paths in life.
This auditorium will be filled
with a new set of friends.
We…
Why do I get the feeling that you've
kept something locked up in your heart?
Son, the moments
that slip away in life never return.
If we stay true to ourselves right now,
we won't regret it later.
So, whether it's happiness or sadness…
Speak your heart.
Don't keep postponing it.
I thought there was a party,
but I don't see anyone around.
Let's begin the party!
- It's not like that.
- Then how?
- Let's go.
- What happened?
Fine, I'll help Uncle.
Okay.
Bro! Why is Lado pissed at you?
We've been fighting.
She blocked me everywhere.
Forget about her.
Where's our guy?
- He's writing.
- What is he writing?
- He's writing a song.
- Song? He never mentioned it.
Yes, bro!
He's going to propose through a song.
Proposal song, you say?
- Oh, damn!
- Wait, I'll be back.
Hey, won't you even say sorry?
- Only I have to initiate it.
- What's your problem?
This is my problem.
When I'm with you,
have you ever put in any effort?
Look at him. For his love,
he's throwing a farewell party for us.
Have you ever
put in any effort like this?
You mean to say
I never did anything for you?
Didn't put in any effort?
Look at this silly girl.
Tell her about that matter.
What matter?
Hey, tell her about the song.
Hey, Lado,
bro has written a song for you.
- Oh, oh!
- Yes, baby.
He's going to sing a song
without stopping for a breath, for you.
- Dude, why would you?
- Is it true?
- Yes, wait and see.
- What are you going to sing?
O beautiful parrot-like one
My beautiful little one
My treasured jewel,
Nesting in my tiny heart
O sculpted beauty…
My sculpted beauty
I want to be known in town
As your lover
I wish to be beside you
When the wedding bells ring
I long to see you
Blush beside me on that day
I want you etched
Beside my heart like a tattoo
I want to recite a poem
Hey, stunning beauty
O ravishing beauty
My stunning beauty,
The moment your eyes open
A single glance,
And you swept into my heart
Like a feast prepared
By a charming beauty
This lovely maiden
Is a spark of sheer bliss
Do you hesitate to confess your love,
Or are you simply spellbound?
Can a girl be just as smitten
As a boy?
Do thoughts of you melt my heart,
Or is it your closeness within?
If it's life's gift,
What more is there to say?
Come set my heart alight
Bring the match and strike it
Come and hold me close
With your father's blessing,
I'll make you mine
Come by my side
Let me proudly show you to my friends
Come, accept my love
Let me make you part of my family
Hey, weren't you supposed
to sing without taking a breath?
Come on, sing.
Oh, yeah, I forgot about it.
I will do it for the next verse.
A bouquet woven
From clustered blooms
A precious gem adorned with pearls
Beholding beauty
That enchants all around
A masterpiece
Adorned with delicate strokes
Graced by the moon's glow
And a river of gold
Beneath the moonlight,
Only truth remains
The joy here is beyond words
Where is your part in this joy,
My dear?
Do we embrace it,
Or set it free?
Will you scorn me,
Or embrace me?
Shall we learn to live in harmony?
Shall we fill our home with children?
Come along, my darling wife
I'll be waiting, eager as ever
A charm too precious to let go
I'll cherish and protect you forever
My stunning beauty,
The moment your eyes open
A single glance,
And you swept into my heart
Like a feast prepared
By a charming beauty
This lovely maiden
Is a spark of sheer bliss
Do you hesitate to confess your love,
Or are you simply spellbound?
Can a girl be just as smitten
As a boy?
Do thoughts of you melt my heart,
Or is it your closeness within?
If it's life's gift,
What more is there to say?
Come set my heart alight
Bring the match and strike it
Come and hold me close
With your father's blessing,
I'll make you mine
Come by my side
Let me proudly show you to my friends
Come, accept my love
Let me make you part of my family...
On that day, we didn't realize
that would be the last day
we were together.
Hereafter, I won't need this key.
I'll miss you, Lado.
- Bye.
Aren't you coming?
I'll cry.
Okay.
Dude, you only have 35 minutes.
Before the Alappuzha Express
steals her away,
you reserve your chance
and confirm your love.
Hey, shut up!
Look, hear me out.
A railway station is the apt place
to propose your love.
Mouna Ragam: Karthik and Revathi.
Dilwale Dulhania Le Jaayenge:
Shahrukh and Kajol.
Then, Kadhal Kottai:
Devayani and Ajith.
A railway station
is the perfect spot to confess your love.
But when I see the railway station,
I only remember Moondram Pirai.
Instead of speaking nonsense, please tell
her those three words without hesitation.
- Okay? Amudha!
- Hey!
He wants to talk to you.
Don't mess it up.
What is it?
You guys keep talking.
Meanwhile, I'll get the platform tickets.
Tell me, Idhaya.
Hand me the bag.
I'll carry it.
- I'm sorry, sir.
- Watch out.
Sorry!
You…
When I see you,
it reminds me
of my friend from college.
Oh, okay, sir.
Are you checking your weight?
No! I'm checking what's in store for me.
What's written on it?
I won't tell.
Show!
Why don't you try?
I don't believe in it.
Please check.
Show!
- Show me the card.
- You didn't show yours.
You did not.
Reverse on me, huh!
Let's go!
All okay?
I got scared
that the train had really started.
So, what's next for you?
Not sure.
I'll get home and figure it out.
I'm going to miss you all.
It felt as though
everything had just begun.
But so soon…
You're going away on the train.
But I don't know why I feel like
I'm going to miss the train.
Before we knew it,
time had flown by.
What are your plans after this?
I have a lot of plans in mind.
But before that…
I would like to tell you
something important…
Do you have water?
No.
Shall I get you some water?
Wait!
- Brother, one bottle.
- What else?
Also, a pack of biscuits.
Here you go.
Hold this.
You're getting a call.
- It's okay, it's Dad. I'll get it later.
- Okay.
I…
I think it's time.
The train is about to leave.
There are still five minutes.
You're very late!
And your watch is slow as well.
The train is about to leave.
Tell her quickly.
Bye, Idhaya.
May all your wishes come true.
I hope all your dreams come true.
All the best.
Take care, okay.
Bye, Idhaya!
Damn you!
Son, you could've told her.
I had a friend named Raja.
Just like you,
he was madly in love.
But he never proposed his love to her.
What happened to him?
It's a long story.
But in these 20 minutes,
you took me back 20 years.
Thanks!
In life, everyone gets only one chance,
but my chance ended
at the railway station.
What are you thinking about?
If I were you,
I'd wonder why I couldn't say
those three words.
You were so close to that girl.
You should've told her, man.
Expressing yourself is easy when
there are no emotional ties involved.
But it's difficult to speak your heart
to someone you love.
Right?
Many people, like me, couldn't
bring themselves to confess their love.
We couldn't express our love.
Or give a reason, either.
Idhaya!
Some things remained only a dream, sir.
Had it become a reality,
it would've been wonderful.
But it never got fulfilled.
Similarly,
I never expressed my love for Amudha.
After that,
life took everyone on different paths.
A few bonds were made.
A few bonds were broken.
Life was running faster than ever.
When I looked back,
five years had gone by.
I'm proud to say
that DTV is entering its fourth year.
Many congratulations
and thank you to one and all.
Guys!
It's time to celebrate!
On this joyous occasion,
I'd like to share a few thoughts.
The work you all have been
doing as a team, once I did it alone.
Installing cable TV in every house.
Collecting payments.
Hosting movie nights on a VCR.
Going from one roof top to another
to repair TV antennas.
In those days,
there was a person who helped me
monitor the clarity of the TV relay.
That's none other than my cute Idhaya.
On this joyous occasion,
I come bearing good news.
We were regional all these years.
Now we'll be participating
in the National Television race.
Now, let's give ourselves
a huge round of applause!
Thank you.
Congratulations, Boss!
Yes, my boy!
Let's celebrate.
Hi! How are you?
How come you're calling?
Do you still remember us?
Dude, this is too much!
Are you at a gym?
Yes! I nailed it
by losing 750 gms in three months.
It's been a long time
since I saw you smile.
Stay like this.
You should always be smiling.
- Wait, I'm adding others.
- Sure, add them.
- Hi!
- Hi, dude.
- Sachin bro!
- When is your wedding?
- Wedding, really?
How? How did you know?
Are you really getting married?
Hey, Dravid, how did you know?
Only two types of men go to the gym.
One who tries to fix himself
after a breakup.
Another who's getting married.
You belong to the second type.
Oh, please wait.
I'll connect Lado.
Hey! Don't do it!
Please take the phone away from her.
Guys, jokes apart.
Next month, on the 24th,
my wedding is in Madurai.
All of you are invited.
We're going to enjoy ourselves
and have fun!
- Fun it is.
- Oh, wait!
You never said who the girl is.
Shit! I forgot to mention.
Her name is Tulasi.
When you guys come down,
I'll introduce her.
- Sure!
- Tulasi?
- Okay, see you guys. Bye!
- Hey!
Please wait!
Let's talk for a while.
It's been a long time
since we laughed over a call.
You're right!
I, too, miss you guys a lot.
But aren't you guys staying
in the same building?
On different floors.
What are you both missing out on?
- You guys must be together all the time.
- Don't get me started.
Idhaya and I work in the same office. He's
on the 3rd floor, I'm on the 2nd floor.
- But it's been 3 weeks since I met him.
- Has it been 3 weeks?
What was the biggest issue
back then for us as students?
Lado and Sachin were on-and-off
in their relationship.
Idhaya had issues confessing his love.
And I had issues sneaking out to
meet him without my family knowing.
Okay! Don't get too emotional.
Come to Madurai,
we'll enjoy for four days.
We're going to enjoy!
- Okay, guys, see you!
- Bye, Idhaya.
Butterflies… are fluttering
A game of hide-and-seek… is on
Don't keep those untold stories
Locked in your heart
Don't keep your passion trapped inside...
Bro, if you don't wear the guard,
even God can't help you.
I ought to!
Express the love in your eyes with words,
And it will blossom
Sorrows faded away
Even the colors celebrate us
My heart echoes your every word
Butterflies are fluttering
A game of hide-and-seek is on
Everything looks lush and green
Beautiful birds circle in our sight
- Hello!
- Hello, son.
Hindu Religious and Charitable Endowments
Minister, Paranthaman speaking.
There are a million ways
for a TV channel to trend in Tamil Nadu.
Instead, you guys are always accusing me,
publishing bad news about me.
Which may infuriate my cadres.
Listen, I may be silent
and won't react to it.
But my cadres won't stay silent.
- So, I'm gently warning you.
- Thanks for your concern, sir.
IDHAYA
- Who are you waiting for?
- Arrow through the heart.
That's me!
- Nephew!
- Uncle!
Welcome!
Seeing the groom,
I thought his friends would be stout,
but you look fit, with a six-pack.
Oh, come on!
That's my niece in the back seat.
She wanted to get a SIM card,
so I brought her along.
Enough reactions.
Please get inside the car.
Take a look
at the Madurai Medical College.
Looks good.
They are very efficient.
You should not be on a diet
when you're in Madurai.
- You must eat your heart's content.
- I understand.
You've come to our
city for the first time.
Let's start by having Jigarthanda.
- Sure.
- Yes, you must have it.
It's harder to get off than getting in.
We've arrived.
Where are you?
First, hear me out.
Do you know who I just saw?
Who?
Hey, Idhaya?
- Yes!
- What are you doing over here?
- Samyuktha…
- Samantha.
Samantha, Hi. How are you?
I'm doing well.
It's been ages since I last saw you.
The last time was at the coaching class.
Now, we are settled in Chennai.
What brings you here?
What's with the formal addressing?
The bride is my cousin.
Wait! Where are your friends?
Everyone is on their way.
Nice, nice!
Sorry, I was on a work call.
That's why I didn't notice you.
That's okay.
In which IT company do you work?
IT company?
I work for NASA!
I work for NASA
in a space research program.
Oh, okay!
Space research, you say?
Yeah, in the space.
Like an astronaut?
Ah, yes.
Sometimes I work as a scientist
and sometimes as an engineer.
But right now we're starting
a new mission.
Wow! Nice!
- What about your twin sister?
- You mean, Samyuktha?
- Yeah, Samyuktha.
- She's married and settled in Australia.
Oh, you guys already know each other.
But I'm used to buying Jigarthanda,
whoever arrives in Madurai.
- Have it.
- Thanks.
- Thanks, Uncle.
- Always listening to music.
- Yes, tell me, bro!
- Idhaya, did you land? Where are you?
- Tell him we're at FAMOUS Jigarthanda.
- I'm here with your uncle.
Step aside in private and talk.
- Excuse me for a minute.
- Please go ahead.
What is it, bro?
I invited Lado to the wedding by mistake.
She has come to create problems.
Now, I don't know what to do.
- So what?
- I can't send someone else to pick her.
Please go and pick her up.
- Hey, don't drag me into this.
- Dude, please help me.
It won't work out.
Please understand. It might
become a huge issue. If you bring her…
I'll manage by saying that
she came with you.
For God's sake, please bring her.
- I can't, bro.
- Please bring her. Bye!
- Bye-bye.
- Hey!
Let's take them for lunch.
- Lunch, right?
- To the Pandian Hotel.
Let's make it a feast.
- Shall we make a move?
- No, I'm returning to the airport.
- Did you lose a bag?
- No, uncle.
An important friend is arriving.
- Friend?
- I must pick them up.
You guys go home. I'll take a cab.
Cab? Why trouble yourself
when we have a car?
Let's bring your friend along.
Let's go together.
It's okay, I can manage.
- Don't feel shy.
- Hey, come on.
We'll have the fish curry
on our way home.
- Shall I come along?
- No, I'll handle it.
Lado, what are you doing here?
Hey, Sachin is getting married.
Let me tell you something.
Sachin does not deserve you.
This is the truth. Understand?
I agree.
But Sachin is getting married.
- What happened?
- Lado.
Sachin's wife's relatives are in the car.
- Wife?
- Please be careful.
He's not yet married,
and you're already calling her his wife.
Then what should I call this?
Does it mean I'm his first wife?
Hello, we're not divorced yet.
- Excuse me, I have to say something.
- Please, Lado!
Sam, look over there.
Looks like they're head over heels
for each other.
The young couple wanted
to come in a cab for privacy.
But I spoiled it by barging in.
Please, please, please. Please, Lado.
Whatever it is, we'll discuss at home.
Okay, fine.
- Pick up my bag.
- Okay.
- Hold this as well.
- Hand it to me.
- Don't say anything, Lado.
- Okay, you shift to the front seat.
Let them take the back seat.
They might get offended.
How do you know the groom, Sachin?
He and I in college--
Uncle, we studied together in college.
That's how we became friends.
- Oh!
- Why aren't you letting me speak?
Listen, we'll go straight to the wedding,
then get back home and discuss further.
After that, we'll go back home.
Understand?
Did you notice, Sam?
I think they'll elope and get married
before Sachin gets married.
We must watch them carefully.
Wow!
Sam, why aren't you bringing the guests?
- You bring them, I have work.
- Fine, I'll do it.
- Hey, Idhaya!
- Hi, uncle.
- When did you arrive?
- I just arrived, Uncle.
Where's your son?
Okay.
- Why is she here?
- Not an issue. I'll handle her.
I'll handle her.
Don't worry about it.
Lado!
What do you mean? How could he
leave the lover who came to meet him?
Let's go inside. Always glaring at me.
Hey, Lado is coming.
How are we going to--
- Hi!
Hi, how are you people?
Where's Sachin? Is he inside?
- Hey, what's happening?
- Hey, not over there.
Wait, our room is over there.
Let's go and freshen up.
- Hey, Sachin's grandma.
- We'll meet her later.
- Where's the groom?
- He is in this room.
Dude!
How are you, bro?
- Excuse me!
- Carry on, son.
Why the hell did you invite Lado?
Dude, I called her when I was high.
I never expected her to show up
and cause problems.
Yeah, as if you're unaware of her traits.
People think she's my girlfriend.
Phew! So, I'm out of trouble then.
Why would it be an issue to you?
I don't exactly have an issue...
Dude!
Handle it for one day.
Tomorrow's my wedding.
Please manage Lado.
- I'll handle it, bro.
- Thank you, dude.
I'm so stressed!
I can't even get married in peace.
You should've thought about it
before you invited her.
Why the heck would they play this song?
Hey, it's our love anthem.
If she hears this…
She'll come down and torture me.
First, switch off this song.
Oh! So, everyone is happily gathered here.
But I've been crying like an idiot inside.
Wow!
The groom's charm is glowing on you.
New shirt, is it? Very nice!
Super!
Hi, Lado! How are you?
Look for yourself. Am I okay?
Look at my face.
Do I look okay?
You tell me.
What's your problem now?
What do you want?
Let's talk.
But first, call off the wedding.
Whatever it is, we'll sit down and talk.
- Okay. Please sit down.
- Are you kidding?
I'm not kidding. I'm serious.
- Let's talk.
- It's not a joke.
Please hear me out.
We'll sort this out.
Let's sit down and talk.
- Please call off the wedding.
- Lado, this is getting out of hand.
- Please wait, Idhaya.
- Let's go, Lado.
- Wait a minute.
- Please hear me out.
- Let me talk to him.
- No...
Idhaya, unlike you
I can't help but express my love.
I'll fight for my love!
Sit down.
Please sit down. Please!
Do you want me to marry you?
If I have to marry you…
Two families
are fast asleep with a wish that
the wedding is at the crack of dawn.
Do you want to ruin their wish
and get married?
Tell me, Lado.
I can understand.
I can understand
that you haven't moved on.
But Lado, please think about
the plight of the other girl.
If you still insist on us getting married…
I'm ready!
I'll do whatever you ask me to.
I will!
I respect you, Lado.
I really respect you.
Lado.
Lado!
In the future, I hope you won't
blackmail me with pictures.
Pig! What did you say?
What did you say?
You ditched me, dude.
I'm going to get married
to a better guy than you.
Someone like Mahesh Babu.
Look at yourself, though.
So, that means Lado
is not your girlfriend.
Nah, she's my friend.
O dainty little parrot
Wrapped in a sari
O slender vine
Adorned with a garland
You're such a rare beauty
That any groom would be captivated
Just one look at you,
And a melody springs to life
You've descended like an angel
Just fold your wings
Let's stand by each other
For a lifetime
Your cheeks are flushed with a deep,
Timeless crimson
Your forehead shines with the deep,
Enduring red of kumkum
Our girl is quite a handful
She won't let anyone have it easy
Our boy is a gem,
So cherish and protect him
She walks in, radiant as jasmine
And magical in her bridal finery
Wherever she sets foot, flowers blossom
She's the little darling
Everyone praises
My darling, my treasure
You are as soothing as sandalwood
Your very being drips with sweetness
You're a bundle of beauty
My golden one,
Just wait until night falls
Even a lion turns into a little mouse,
Circling only around you
I'll give you every star in the sky
Give me that forelock
That grazes your brow
Even all the care you show me
Can never satisfy my longing
She stands beside me,
Grazing me like royalty
You bewitching beauty
Your smile leaves me love-struck
You're as sweet as a laddu,
Covered in beauty spots
My darling, my treasure
You are as soothing as sandalwood
Your very being drips with sweetness
You're a bundle of beauty
My golden one,
Just wait until night falls
Even a lion turns into a little mouse,
Circling only around you
Look at this handsome boy.
Where are you going, son?
- Stand in one place.
- My dear boy.
What happened?
Such a beautiful boy.
Come!
What happened?
Where are you going?
Remember the pani puri shop
next to the coaching class?
Yeah, I remember.
I feel like having their pani puri.
Who would go all the way to Trichy
just to have pani puri?
I will go!
Ah, sorry!
Idhaya, if you see anyone coming,
give me a signal.
Okay.
Sam!
I too feel like having pani puri.
- Hi, brother, how are you?
- I'm good.
- Your shop looks different now.
- Yes, son.
- Super!
- I thought you said two would be enough.
Sriram, why did you
join the coaching class?
Aren't you here for Pradeepa?
The classes will end in two weeks.
When will you tell her?
Oh, baby,
You be taking my breath away
Hey, come on, come here
I'll keep knockin' your door
Are you the gift fate gave me?
Oh, baby,
You be taking my breath away
Hey, come on, come here
Until I really feel
The thrill of first love
Are you the gift fate gave me?
What are you looking for?
I had carved my name.
- Was that your bench?
- Yes.
You get up.
Yeah, you! Stand up!
Get up! Get up!
State Newton's second law.
Acceleration of an object
is directly proportional to its net force.
F=ma
How come you still remember it?
I studied hard.
How could I forget?
I didn't know you liked pani puri so much.
Come to Chennai. I'll take you
to Sowcarpet and buy you lots of it.
Pani puri?
I have a flight to catch tomorrow.
I'm heading back to the US.
- Not sure when I'll return.
- Tomorrow?
Yeah!
Hey, wait.
There are missed calls from Dad.
Idhaya, it's getting late.
Let's go!
- Hey, groomsmen, where are you guys?
- We're at the office. You?
I'm at the Chennai airport.
Why are you always at an airport?
Stop kidding.
Sam is leaving for America.
So we came to send her off.
You own a THAR SUV,
but you're driving it like a cab.
After dropping her off,
come to the office.
Sure!
- I want to go to the airport.
- Why airport?
Brother said he will come here.
Why should we go?
- I'm in love with Sam.
- Hey!
- Why suddenly?
- It's not sudden!
Why would I meet her and hang out
in Madurai after so many years?
Everything in life happens for a reason.
If I miss this chance…
I don't think
I will get another chance to tell her.
That's not what I meant.
But all of a sudden…
I cannot repeat the same mistake.
- Hey, we're coming along.
- Dude, wait for us.
Check how long until the flight leaves.
There's an hour left.
Hey, will you surely propose to her?
I will propose to her.
We have an hour left.
We'll arrive on time.
Sir, there's so much space here.
You could walk on the side. Why are you
shoving me? Which office do you work in?
Hey! There are many leaders
and politicians in the city.
You spare them all
but you're publishing news about my Chief.
Hey! I ought to!
What a timing. Oh, no!
Sir, I'm sorry.
I know who sent you.
I'm aware of why you are here.
But I'm urgently heading to the airport.
I'll be back in two hours.
Then, we'll discuss it.
Why don't you wait upstairs?
Hey, do we look like an auto
or taxi to put us on wait?
Sir, just give me two hours.
Hey, I want justice for my chief!
Sir, please go upstairs and sit.
Hey, what's your problem?
Excuse me,
how do I get to Accenture office?
- Sir, one minute.
- Hey!
- Accenture isn't here.
- You must head to that side.
- Not that side. But this side.
How is it even on this side?
- Sir, which way did you enter?
- Hey, hop in!
- Hop in, damn it!
- Hey, don't let them escape.
Hey, stop! Catch him!
Hey, start the car!
Catch him!
Hey, don't you have any road sense?
Step out of the car.
- Sir, sir, sir, sorry, sir.
- Step out of the car.
Sir, I'm sorry.
- Look, what have you done?
- Dude, you handle it.
- Go, catch them.
- Prabhu, you handle it.
Guys, you leave. I'll handle it.
Fine, handle him.
Look at yourself. Stop, damn it!
Hey, where are you going?
Stop!
Hey, how did you get in?
- Brother, is the bus going to the airport?
- Yes!
Take your seat.
- Super!
- Hey, who are you guys?
I'm a Shardul Thakur fan.
- Yes!
- Does he even have fans?
CSK runs in my blood.
If you slit his hands
he will bleed yellow.
Hey, you guys step off the bus
and do whatever you want.
Step off the bus
or else they'll fire me.
Brother, you'd only lose your job.
But my friend would lose his life.
It's a matter of love.
Love?
Hey, who's kissing the bonnet?
- Mumbai Indians, bro.
- Hey!
- Brother, eyes on the road!
- Oh, no!
Sir, he's a CSK fan.
Please spare him.
Hey, you proved
that you're a Shardul Thakur fan.
- You're getting thrashed.
- Please drive faster.
Hey, he's hanging like garlands
on a pilgrimage bus.
That's enough.
- Happy journey.
- Thank you.
Brother, he curled up
after getting thrashed by us.
Where do I bring him?
Hey, lift him.
CSK may be at the bottom
of the point table.
But suddenly, it'll shift to top gear
and move up.
Hey, we've arrived at the airport.
When are you going to finish the game?
Wait! Let me end it right away.
They already thrashed
and stuck him to the bonnet.
Yet he's determined to fight.
Stop it!
Buddy!
Stop it! You might kill him.
We're getting late for the flight.
They tore the bus seats.
I'm going to get fired.
I don't know what to do.
Hey, no, no!
Please don't record and post reels.
They'll fire me.
Time came to a standstill
We've been stealing glances every day
My steps always find their way to you
Sleep has deserted me
My yearning keeps growing
My body trembles because of you,
My love
Hey, come on, come here
Are you the gift fate gave me?
Just your thoughts
Lift me off the ground
Just you… only you…
I'll stay by your side forever
You smile every day
Till your lips hurt
Oh, baby, you be taking my breath away
Pushing me far away
Making me drift away
Teasing me every day
I'll keep knockin' your door
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Idhaya, what are you doing?
An unspoken love, raging within
An endless quest,
A heart filled with unrest
Will this wound ever heal
If we stay silent?
Will I overcome my shyness?
Will love prevail?
I'm still clueless about why
I ran onto the runway like a madman.
Perhaps I didn't want
to miss another opportunity with her.
But one good thing that came out of it
was that Juju came back into my life.
I thought my feelings for her
ended after that.
After that, back to square one.
My uncle was afraid
I would end up alone like him.
That's why he kept
insisting that I get married.
But then one day…
I realized that she was beyond my reach.
Hey, hey, hey, stop it!
Stop it! I am done!
- He's never going to propose.
- Sir, where are you going?
What do you expect?
I've been waiting for him
to propose at least once,
but he is not doing it.
Thrash him, sir.
Sir, you made it till here.
Please listen to the rest of the story.
It'll be terrific!
Another love?
- I can't bear it anymore. Spare me.
- Please, sir.
Sir, it's not another love story.
- He's getting engaged.
- Yes, sir.
- Engagement? Engagement?
You never mentioned it.
I was expecting another tragedy
like the film Punnagai Mannan.
- Girl, please make me a drink.
- Plus one!
We all convinced him somehow.
As per Uncle's wish,
we got him engaged to Adhithi.
He too accepted it and moved on.
Hey, stop it!
Hey, at least wear shades
before checking girls out.
- It's so evident you're looking.
- Is it?
Here you go.
Where's your wife?
She's putting on makeup.
The engagement is over.
What is she getting ready for now?
Let her take her sweet time.
Let it go.
Sounds good!
I am confused if he's happy or sad.
He keeps an expression that
fits all kinds of background scores.
- Something is wrong.
- Hey...
He's doing well. Don't mess it up.
- I feel something's wrong.
- I too feel the same.
Let's ask him.
Hey, all okay?
Yeah, all okay.
All okay, it seems.
He's fine.
But you guys are confusing him.
What's the secret?
You see, a lot of your friends
have come down from Bangalore.
We're friends. They're friends, too.
If all the friends mingle…
I hope you understood.
But aren't you married?
He got married.
I never got married.
We two are bachelors!
- They are both single.
- Idhaya, please tell her.
They aren't married.
I only got married once.
- Hey, Idhaya!
- Hi, Adhithi.
- Have you reached?
- I reached.
- Where exactly are you?
- I'm right here. Where are you?
I'm just parking my car.
- You?
- I'm on the first floor.
Super, I'll see you there.
Idhaya!
What a surprise!
It's been years
since we last saw each other.
How are you?
Oh, my God! Look at you.
You've changed a lot, Idhaya.
Are you still in touch
with your college friends?
Sachin, Lado, Prabhu, Dravid…
Those days were a lot of fun.
Sorry, I couldn't keep in touch.
I miss those days.
How are you?
I'm doing well.
I now work at Delhi AIMS.
I came to Chennai to attend a conference.
I never expected to run into you.
Did you get married?
Not yet. But going to.
You haven't changed, Idhaya.
You're still the same.
A man of few words. Silent.
You're the same!
Anyway, I'm leaving.
I'll see you.
Bye.
If you don't mind,
I want to tell you something.
Back in college…
I was in love with you.
But I didn't know
if you felt the same way about me.
With the fear of rejection,
I could not confess my love.
I was planning to tell you
at the railway station.
But I couldn't do it.
But now…
I feel very happy.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm happily married.
I have two beautiful kids.
It's just that…
I felt like telling you.
And I'm glad I could.
I'm okay!
Bye!
Please don't forget to invite me
for your wedding.
Fine! Bye, Idhaya.
Bye!
- Hello?
- Lado, listen.
I'm coming to the US to meet Sam.
Are you even in your senses?
You're about to get married.
Why would you do something like this?
The pain of rejection is nothing compared
to the pain of leaving your love unspoken.
Didn't you say that you
got to fight for your love?
I'm not in a situation to fight.
Even if I did,
it won't be the right thing to do.
At least let me speak my heart out.
Are you going to say
"you loved her" or "in love with her?"
Why are you asking me?
Ask Adhithi's family about it.
Call her father.
Instead, you're calling me.
Hey, I asked you a question.
- Hey, Senthil, come here.
- Hey, are you there?
Hello?
I'm going to say, "I loved her."
She's now my past, Lado.
If you think you'd feel better
after speaking your heart out,
then come over here.
We'll handle it.
Now, you say?
No! Get married to Adhithi
and bring her too.
Then you can tell her
"love you" together.
Come soon!
The wedding is in 10 days.
What excuse can I make?
You have your bachelor party.
Use that as an excuse.
Everyone will be
more than happy to come along.
I will handle the rest.
You just come.
Hey, don't make strong drinks
and get him sloshed.
- We have a lot of work to do.
- My mixing is perfect, dude.
Uncle!
I will ask you something.
Don't get worked up.
You first ask. Then I'll decide
whether to get worked up or not.
Uncle, here's your drink.
- Guys are asking for a bachelor party.
- Go ahead, throw one.
Take them away.
Not here, but in the US.
Do you mean
the United States of America?
I will return two days before the wedding.
- You want to go?
- Yes, Uncle.
Take permission from Adhithi.
Why should I ask for her permission?
Go to her. She's going to be your wife.
You need her permission.
- You tell me, Uncle.
- Don't feel shy.
Go and get her permission.
- What is this, Uncle?
- Go ahead! Stop thinking.
Idhaya, I don't have a passport.
Why don't we go to Goa?
Hey, get lost!
Go have a fun trip.
You don't need my permission.
We will be returning only
two days before the wedding.
I was checking as it'll be
a close call to the wedding.
We can manage.
- Hi, Dad.
- What is the son-in-law saying?
You see, I was telling her…
There's a business deal happening
in America.
Trump has given him
an appointment to meet.
Oh!
He is asking if it is right
to go with the wedding close by.
Trump, right?
Please go and meet him.
You will return
before the wedding, right?
- I will, Father-in-law.
- Then go ahead.
Why do you look stunned?
Trump, he says.
It's usual in politics.
Listen, when he returns from the US…
Print a banner, "The Minister's son-in-law
is returning after meeting Trump."
- This is usual in politics as well.
- Right!
You guys carry on.
Thanks.
I'll miss you, Idhaya.
You guys are such close friends.
At least you guys could've
helped him confess his love.
You're right. Had I helped him,
it wouldn't have been a problem now.
Now, you realize.
Tomorrow he's getting married.
Go to sleep.
I'm going to sleep.
Looks like someone hasn't moved on.
He's not worth that right now.
I'm just a nice person, you know.
Sir, do you know
what happened in America?
Hey, I'll throw you out of the plane.
- Shut up and sleep.
- Okay, sir.
Bro, close your eyes and sleep for a bit.
No matter what,
only good things will happen.
Sleep.
Hey, what did you say
happened in America?
From what I'm hearing,
I don't think we're returning to India.
I had a doubt when you brought us out
so far for the bachelor party.
That you must've done something.
I get a feeling that he's here to convert
his Aadhaar Card into a Green Card.
What's the purpose of telling her
that you loved her?
You're right!
I don't know. It's been pricking
my conscience for a while now.
That too after Amudha spoke to me…
The feeling became stronger.
When a married woman mustered
the courage to speak her heart…
I cannot keep this locked in my heart,
get married, and lead a new life.
For two days, leave me alone.
I'll meet Sam…
If I tell her, I'd feel light, guys.
At the end of the day, it's still
my bachelor's party, so have fun.
- Correct!
- Okay!
We're convinced.
Let's enjoy the trip.
Hi!
Wait, I'll come out.
Tell me, what are you doing here?
I am here on a small business trip.
At NASA?
I have a meeting in New York.
I had some time to kill,
so I came to look around NASA.
Not bad!
Are you interested in NASA and astronomy?
It's all because of you.
Oh, oh!
Since school, you've shown
interest in space, rocket science, etc.
Back then,
I thought you lied about it.
But not bad.
You've come a long way, Sam.
Thank you.
You know, it's been six months
since I saw a known face.
Seeing you here feels like
I traveled to Madurai.
Suddenly, I'm missing everyone.
Maybe that's why I'm here.
What did you say?
Nothing!
Don't you use this rocket
for your missions?
We just returned from a mission.
- Oh!
- So, we're on a break now.
We're currently conducting
Stem-Programs for students.
Wow! Super!
Actually,
I'll be visiting New York this weekend.
If you're free, we can catch up.
Unless you're with someone.
No, no! I'm here alone.
Okay! I'll see you in New York.
O heart of mine
Are you the spark that sows love?
Your heart carries countless stories
O heart of mine
Are you the spark that sows love?
Your heart carries countless stories
Who are you, wayfarer?
You're but a passing traveler
Feet that won't take flight,
Eyes that cannot soar
Why soar across the sky
To reach the distant beyond?
Blooms unfold in every direction,
Filling the world with vibrant hues
Every path I find here
Sets my restless heart adrift
Hey, Idhaya,
Don't flutter like a butterfly
Hey, my heart,
Don't grow weary thinking about it
Don't lose yourself
Searching for what lies ahead
Idhaya, don't squander your happiness
What is it that you need?
Tell me, won't you?
Keep fighting,
And you'll make it yours
You're lightning itself
So why this heart of stone?
I left you and soared away,
Yet my heart was brought to its knees
You're going away
You're my very soul, aren't you?
Let my heart beat louder than ever
Let the dream lingering in my eyes
Fall into my hands
May this faltering heart tell our story
May everything in our lives
Unfold beautifully
O heart of mine...
Hey, Sis, did you reach Chennai?
Yeah, I reached!
What are you up to?
I'm heading out.
Where are you heading?
To propose my love.
- Damn you, girl!
- I don't know if you remember.
He used to come to the same
coaching and tennis classes.
He even visited our house on our birthday.
- Idhaya!
- Oh, that guy!
He used to check me out at coaching class.
He would've checked you out,
thinking it was me.
How come suddenly you're in love?
It's not easy to impress you.
You know, when someone
keeps crossing paths in your life…
It may not be a coincidence.
I feel it's more than that.
These corny dialogues
don't work even in cinemas now.
Am I right, baby?
You're demotivating me.
I'm hanging up.
He's leaving tomorrow.
I must propose to him tonight.
- All the best.
- Thanks, Sis.
We postponed our tickets three times now.
Uncle has been calling me continuously.
Only if we leave tomorrow will it work.
If not, forget about your wedding.
Give me some time to think.
What are you thinking about?
What more do you want to think about?
You're feeling emotional,
as if it were a fresh proposal.
You're going to tell
that you loved her, right?
Or do you love her?
Hey, you promised me.
Dude, this does not involve emotions.
You're here just to share information.
Bear that in mind.
From the looks of it…
I feel it's not his past love
but his present love.
Hey, Prabhu, don't encourage him.
He's already engaged.
Who's going to explain to Adhithi?
Only we're discussing it.
He's sitting here silently.
Hey, open your mouth
and say something.
Dude, you hung out for ten days
with her to your heart's desire.
Now don't go and propose to her.
That'll mess with her mind.
Your wedding is the day after.
Dude, use inky-pinky-ponky and
choose who you'd want to live with.
He might do it.
Please shut up.
Will you all please stop talking?
Hey, first, do what you came here for.
Tell Sam about your wedding.
After that, we'll leave for India.
Hey, Idhaya, we're talking to you.
Say something, damn it.
Idhaya, please say something.
Everyone is asking you.
Answer them, Idhaya.
I'm sure you have a lie ready
for this situation, too.
These ten days,
how much have you lied to me?
"I came to meet an investor.
I came alone. I'm single."
Sam, you've misunderstood him.
You guys, please don't say anything.
Weren't you guys in on it?
I've never met a horrible person like you.
Sam!
Sam! Sam!
Sam, please hear me out.
What more do you have
to lie about, Idhaya?
Go ahead.
I did not lie, Sam.
Look, I came here specifically to see you.
I don't get it!
How could you meet me when
you're getting married in a few weeks?
You've misunderstood me, Sam.
You're getting it all wrong.
Only now do I understand it clearly.
You're here to celebrate
your bachelor's party.
And all you want
is a girl to have fun with.
You freaking used me.
Listen! Your anger is fair.
I should've told you
about my wedding on the first day.
But I don't know why I didn't.
You've said it now. I'm leaving!
Sam! Sam, please let me speak.
At least, hear me out.
What's left to talk about, Idhaya?
You hung out with me for ten days.
Next, you'd invite me to your wedding.
No…
Do I look like a bitch to you?
At least be true to the girl
you're getting married to, Idhaya.
I don't care what you think about me, Sam.
I'll say what I came here to say.
Listen, I've always been--
Even now, you're only
thinking about yourself.
You never considered my feelings.
Get lost!
Hey, that's mine.
As it is, you're carrying
too much baggage.
And you want mine, too.
Give it to me.
- Okay.
- Sir.
You're leaving without saying anything.
- Oh, I forgot! Happy married life!
- I didn't mean that.
Sir, sir, sir, sir!
So, sir, where are you
headed for breakfast?
Madhampatty Rangaraj Catering.
You could come to the wedding.
- No, no, no, no!
- Please join us, sir.
My body can't take another plot twist.
I have a lot of work.
Spare me!
- Bye, bye, bye!
- Sir, please!
Where are you?
I've arrived!
- I'm at the exit gate.
- I'm at the arrival gate.
Where are you?
Teacher!
Hey, that's Geetha teacher.
- Teacher!
- Who is she?
- It's our Geetha teacher.
She's our favorite teacher.
- Geetha teacher?
- Yes, Geetha teacher.
He left a pregnant woman alone
on the verge of delivery.
He must be a classic jerk.
Is this what you guys felt about him?
Sorry, ma'am, we were young,
and it was unintentional.
Not an issue.
What have you decided now?
I don't know.
Do whatever your heart says, Idhaya.
Ma'am, your husband says
that he's got some work.
At least you can come
to Idhaya's wedding.
- It'll be fun!
- Yeah, you should.
If you let them, they would narrate
a flashback to everyone.
Your uncle is waiting.
Leave!
- Sir?
We're more than this.
No! Leave now!
Hey, let's go.
- See you, Teacher.
- Bye.
Bye.
See you!
Even on the wedding day,
you guys arrive late.
They'll be here soon!
Look, they've arrived.
Welcome. Please, welcome.
- Greetings.
- In-law!
Oh, he has arrived.
That's great!
Hi!
Dear, greet him.
You keep me on my toes
until the last minute.
We're here now! Let's go inside!
Hi, Priya!
Welcome, Son-in-law.
Usually, people wait for me
at the assembly.
But now you have made me wait for you.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay. Please come in.
Guys, shall we take the groom now?
- Please take him.
- Come on, let's go.
Hey, hey! Hey, hey!
Why are guys coming in batches?
Where is your luggage?
- The luggage is in the room.
- Did you bring the liquor?
- We never bought one.
- I asked you to get it duty-free.
- Uncle, here I come.
- Why is he going without being called?
I think they didn't buy it.
Hi!
Uncle, I want to talk to you.
Hey, Idhaya, are you kidding?
All the city's VIPs are here.
How could you even think
of calling off the wedding?
Only after you said yes
did I go ahead with this marriage.
You were with that girl
for the past six months
but now you don't want her.
What would people think about us?
Forget people.
What do I tell Adhithi?
Have I ever said no to anything
you've asked of me?
Or have I forced you to do anything?
Please understand the situation.
Adhithi is the right match for you.
When we don't get what we wish for,
it does hurt.
But if we don't get what we need,
our life will be ruined.
Please understand.
Look, I'm not just your uncle,
I'm your parent as well.
If you feel the same way,
for God's sake, come to the wedding.
It's time! They're calling for the groom.
Hey, I'll be out! Get lost!
You want me to call off this wedding?
Okay.
No matter what, I'll face everything.
You don't worry about it.
I'll handle it. I'll face it.
Fine!
Not an issue. I'll handle it.
Uncle, bring me my wedding clothes.
I'll be ready in five minutes.
Idhaya, I'll convince everyone.
You don't have to say anything.
I'm at fault.
You go ahead. I'll follow shortly.
Listen, don't confuse yourself.
I want only what you wish for.
Am I right, Son?
Okay.
- Sachin bro, you are saved for now.
- Yes, Dravid!
Hey, Uncle!
I upheld my promise
and brought Idhaya on time.
I understood your plan.
What plan?
You're pretending to get ready for the
wedding but you're planning to cancel it.
Isn't that your plan?
If I were in your situation,
I would've planned the same.
What's the point of friendship
if you don't
help your friend be with the one he loves?
I won't let it happen.
He will get married to Adhithi.
That's good for him,
and he has understood it.
I expect you guys
to understand it as well.
Instead, if you think of
doing something stupid…
I won't spare you guys.
Hey!
- You look suspicious to me.
- Don't worry about me, Uncle.
How come we didn't think about
what Uncle just said about Idhaya?
It's our duty to help Idhaya
unite with his true love.
Only then are we responsible friends.
We're not good friends, dude.
- Damn!
- What can we do about it now?
We'll cancel the wedding.
We unite Idhaya and Samantha.
Okay, we'll unite them!
- Yeah, we'll unite them.
- Yes, guys!
I won't let it happen!
Hey, Team America.
I'm Team Adhithi.
- Adhithi?
- Yes!
I will make sure your plan fails
and unite Adhithi and Idhaya.
I swear on Uncle.
I'm leaving!
Hey, Juju!
- Hey Juju!
- Hey!
Brother, ignore him.
He's pissed off because we didn't
get him whiskey from the US.
- Let's follow our plan.
- Guys, please focus.
We only have two hours left.
Let's go!
Many VIPs are dining tonight.
Make sure to add
plenty of dried fruit in the dessert.
Set dried fruits aside.
There are more pressing issues to tend to.
Take a look.
What the hell is this?
- Sir.
- He's my friend.
Still, it's a matter of a girl's life.
Please manage to stop this wedding
and save a girl's life.
- Hey! Hey!
- Take a look at this, sir.
- Two people!
- How did this happen?
I've never touched another woman
other than my wife.
I don't understand how I ended up
putting my arms around these girls.
- It's AI.
- What does it mean?
Using this, we can make a good person
look bad, and a bad person look good.
Also, we can turn truth into a lie
and a lie into truth.
We can do anything we want.
They're from a news channel.
They're planning to get
you trapped in a scandal.
- The groom is a noble person like you.
- Damn, he's ruining our plan.
Thank goodness you saved me.
I almost believed them.
Hey, he explained that it's all AI.
I know now.
Mind your business!
Team America -0.
Team Adhithi -1.
- I'll meet you in round 2.
- Hey, what's wrong with him?
Dude, come on, let's plan something else.
- Hi, bro!
- Greetings, are you the DJ?
- Greetings, I'm the DJ.
Bro, you must play a song now.
That should make the groom throw away
the garland and run off the stage.
It should move him.
I got you, bro!
What kind of song?
"All of me, someone like you…"
Like these songs?
- If you play these, they'll doze off.
- Is it?
Please play the songs on this list.
Everything else will happen on its own.
- Bro.. I got you, brother.
- Play it!
I got you.
O Heart of mine
You're one of a kind
My throbbing love
For wisdom and flesh alike,
The journey is endless
Every dream whispers to the heart...
So, you lied to me and went to America.
That's not the problem now.
Give me an idea to call off the wedding.
Bro, what kind of songs are you playing?
It doesn't give any wedding vibes.
Bro, I know what to do.
Don't tell me how to do my job.
If you keep up this nonsense…
Only the equipment will leave this place,
not you.
- Bro, bro, bro, bro…
- Play rocking songs!
Bro, I'm bad at this language.
Language is never a problem.
The song should be rocking!
I think this should work for you, brother.
Sit here.
Hello!
- It's very wrong of you.
- What did I do wrong?
You should've gone with Idhaya.
He called you along for moral support.
It was wrong of you to avoid him.
It's his life.
He must make a decision.
Oh!
It was your wife and child.
But he never waited,
thinking it was your responsibility.
You don't have the magnanimity
that young kid had.
Are you seriously comparing me to him?
You didn't want to take a leave
when I went into labor.
But he signed the form and was with me.
To you, the Swiss were important.
To him, his teacher was important.
You were running to build a future.
But he came looking for his teacher.
- He was there with me--
- Dear, please stop!
The more you talk,
my ears are ringing with
a melodramatic background score.
I'm convinced.
We'll leave right away for the wedding.
- Lado, decorations look good.
- Hello, ma'am.
What's going to happen now?
- The wedding will happen.
- Sir?
Madhampatty Catering.
I'm going to feast today.
- Sir, what do we do?
- Thank you.
What's with sassing?
We brought the love of his life to him.
If this does not bowl him over,
I don't know what else would.
Let's see!
Son, Son-in-law, my daughter's groom,
our pride and the King of our family.
You are a masterpiece beyond compare,
a garland of fragrance,
a haven of joy,
and a grove that offers solace.
Sheesh! Will he finish it today?
Despite being busy with the wedding,
in order to develop his business,
he went to America
and met President Trump.
Your sincerity and hard work
have stunned me.
Sir, he's a martyr
who sacrificed his love for his Uncle.
Yeah, right.
Martyrs don't get girls, only a pension.
He's an old timer. Scrap material.
What do we do now?
Is there no other option?
- There's an option.
- What is it, sir?
I must appreciate his Uncle
for raising an honest person.
- Sir?
- Let me appreciate him.
- Sir!
- Sachin, my bro!
Nice to see you again, sir.
Uncle, he's our friend.
- Surya!
- Hello, Surya!
You both are exceptional.
I've never seen such a great
uncle-and-nephew combo.
- He's gold, sir.
- Gold, sir. Truly gold.
In this day and age,
no one would sacrifice
the woman he loves for his uncle.
But he did!
Don't be afraid.
I won't speak like my father.
You sacrificed your life for his sake.
I'm sure he would sacrifice
the love of his life for you.
But there's one thing…
His heart will be crying.
Eventually, he'll be okay.
You have done a lot for him.
This is very small compared
to what you did for him.
He'll be okay.
Okay, sir. I'll be around.
I'll stay until everything is over.
Greetings to all.
Today is my nephew, Idhaya's wedding.
He is both a blessing and a cherished
relationship bestowed upon me by God
so that I don't end up lonely
in this world.
For 30 years now,
we have lived for each other.
Until now,
he has never asked me for anything.
He probably felt that I would be upset
if he asked for it.
Such a gem of a boy, my Idhaya,
for the first time,
he asked me for something
from the bottom of his heart.
But I denied him.
But he was not upset about it.
The life he rightfully deserves,
he threw it away
to uphold his respect for my word
and is sitting here to get married.
If I still remain silent,
whatever I did till date for him
would hold no meaning.
Dear Adhithi, please forgive me.
I know what you would go through
if this wedding is called off.
Hey!
But if we go through with this wedding,
neither of you will be happy
even for a moment in your lives.
What's happening?
Everyone on the stage, please forgive me.
If you could graciously
cancel this wedding,
- and help him start his new life...
- What's happening out here?
Are you kidding me?
Hey, Siva Subramaniam, come here.
Nothing's wrong, Chief.
Please wait a minute.
There's been a confusion.
Nothing's wrong.
- Adhithi, nothing is wrong.
- Adhithi!
Dad, hold on!
Making a fuss
won't make this wedding happen.
Even if we make it happen,
how do I marry someone who
does not love me and make a life with him?
Sorry, sir, please forgive me.
- You came here to bless us.
- It's okay, dear.
But…
I'm sorry,
this wedding is not happening anymore.
Please forgive us.
Is the wedding over?
I didn't hear the nuptial beats.
To call off the wedding,
you brought his lover.
Did you ever consider my plight?
I only thought about your life.
For whose benefit do you think
I called off the wedding?
It's for your good.
Hand it to me.
Are you saying he's a bad man?
Nah, he's a good man.
That's the problem.
But don't assume
that he's smart and romantic.
Even if he's held at gunpoint,
he can't romance.
Actually, I saved you.
You owe me, bro.
Are you trying to convince me?
On the flight, I listened to his
entire flashback for 16 hours.
Even 20 years weren't enough for him
to propose to the love of his life.
He has to fall in love with you
and then propose...
Imagine for yourself
how long it will take.
You escaped!
Girl, that's my cigarette.
Go and complete what's left.
We have to end with "All is well."
Make it up for what you lost
in the coaching class.
- Where's your twin sister?
- Twin sister?
Not bad! You identified me.
- I don't repeat my mistakes.
- Are you not Samantha?
- Hey…
- Are you serious?
Did you know?
I couldn't spot the difference.
Hello.
Sir, you kept us in the dark
and surprised us.
Look, we only had two hours,
and I brought who I could.
Whatever, we called off the wedding.
Well done!
Hey, Idhaya!
Is she not the girl?
Then who's the girl?
This girl's sister.
- Where is she now?
- In America.
Oh, God, please save me from them.
Chill, Uncle.
We'll take care of it in the sequel.
ALL IS WELL
Hey, what's your problem?
Didn't I tell you already?
He's a good boy.
Hey, shut up.
I know him well.
We all approve of him.
What have you decided now?
Hey, stop with your drama.
We noticed how cozy you guys were
in New York.
You guys have sung a duet.
Do you still expect him
to make the first move?
You're right!
You want him to come?
Oh, so the entire gang is here.
You can talk all you want.
I reckon he's out there.
Ask him
to look me in the face and propose.
I'll forget about everything.
Dude, come over here.
- Hi, Sam!
- Finally, you appeared.
Except for you, everyone else
is saying that you're in love with me.
This call will last
only for another 40 seconds.
Now's the time for you to say it.
They've switched on the theatre lights.
Hey, look at me.
Rolling credits of the crane operator
is on screen now.
For God's sake,
propose before the rolling titles end.
The audience has started
to look for parking tickets.
Please say it.
I'm feeling shy looking at you
being all shy.
Say it!
Idhaya…
He won't propose. Please leave.
He's never going to muster the courage.
Everyone, please shut up.
I'm going to say it.
I'll handle it.
Super!
Sam…
I--
I…